number one.
The doctor you are a doctor in a hospital.
At the hospital there are two patients, one patient
Which is 90 years old and a patient who is 20 years old.
Both have the same deadly illness and are only expected to live for another month.
But there is a cure
That can save them and you have this cure.
But the problem is that there is only enough for one person.
What are you doing?
Do you give the cure to the older patient and let him live the few
years he has left and sacrifices the young patient?
For a life is probably no more worthwhile
something else?
Number two dungeons.
You stand at a cliff and at the edge of the cliff hangs one
Foreign pregnant woman and stays stuck.
She will soon lose grip.
If you don't help her up a few feet away from her hangs
Your best friend, also unable to get up on your own.
How they ended up there is unimportant in this context,
But now it is important to choose who to save.
If you save the woman then your best friend falls down and dies.
Would you step aside and let your best friend
And the person you enjoy continuing to socialize?
Although it is incredibly painful for you?
Or would you fight for your love and try to prevent them from meeting
and risk losing your lifelong friendship?
What weighs heavier than your own happiness and jealousy
Or their potential happiness together?
Write in the comments what you
answers and if you can justify why.
If you have missed part, I put it as a link in the description.
And as always, thank you for watching!